releaseday.com 2014-08-17

# Privacy Policy | Releaseday

**How does Releaseday use information it collects from or about me?**

  * Payment Information

We use payment information such as credit card numbers, as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service (for example, processing payments from our Releaseday’s subscribers) and to prevent abuse of the Releaseday services.

  * Other Information

Releaseday may use other information provided by you for: contacting you; customizing the content and advertising you view; fulfilling your requests for products or services; identifying content you share when you use the Releaseday Services; improving our services; conducting research; compiling aggregate data for internal and external business purposes; preventing potentially illegal activities; protecting our rights; other uses in accordance with our Terms of use and for any other purpose disclosed to you at the time we collect your information.

  * Informing you of any new features ,and value added services you will need to know on Releaseday.com

  * Recommendations and Advertising

We (and service providers acting on our behalf) may use information about you, including your use of Releaseday, to provide recommendations and advertisements on Releaseday.

**With whom does RD share the information it collects from or about me?**

  * Other Releaseday Users.

The Releaseday Services include social features that let you interact with other people who use them. Information that you voluntarily make public on Releaseday via any medium will be shared with other Releaseday users. You can control the sharing of certain information contained in your Releaseday profile in the [Privacy and Settings page](https://www.releaseday.com/user-account/privacyPolicy).

  * Social Networking Services.

You can use the Releaseday Services on other social networking services such as Facebook, and connect your Releaseday account with your social networking account. With your consent, Releaseday may send information about you to these social networking services, including information about the videos you watch and your activities on the Releaseday Services.

  * Service Providers.

We may also share your information with companies that provide services to us, including companies that assist with payment processing, website, user, and business analytics, data processing, account management, advertising, and other services. We may enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows us to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive while using the Releaseday Services. However, our agreements with these service providers limit the types of information these companies collect, how they may collect it, and how they may use it.

  * Other Parties When Required By Law or When Necessary to Protect Your Rights or Ours.

There may be instances when we may disclose your information without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of Releaseday or its affiliates, and each of their respective investors, directors, officers, employees, agents, and suppliers; to protect the safety and security of users of the Releaseday or to enforce our Terms of Use; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity, whether or not legally required. If you notify us that you believe your legal rights have been violated by Releaseday or another user of the Releaseday Services, we may provide the information that you provide to us to others to the extent that we believe it is necessary to evaluate and respond to your complaint. For instance, if you submit a notice of copyright infringement to us, we may send a copy to the person or entity who uploaded, stored, or transmitted the material addressed by the communication.

  * Other Parties In Connection With a Transfer of Assets.

If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your information to one or more third parties as part of that transaction.

  * Other Parties With Your Consent.

In addition to the sharing described in this Privacy Policy, and only with your consent, we may share personally identifiable information about you, for example, your name, address, telephone number, or email address, with other parties.

**How does Releaseday protect the information it collects from or about me?**  
We use reasonable physical, technical, and administrative measures to safeguard information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification.. We also take steps to ensure that only those Releaseday employees, agents, and contractors who have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your information are granted access.  
Despite these efforts, please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident using the Releaseday Services but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

**What happens when Releaseday changes its Privacy Policy?**  
From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law or changes to the scope of the Releaseday Services or for other reasons. Therefore, it is important to check the effective date of the Privacy Policy posted at **http://www.Releaseday.com/privacy-policy** each time you visit Releaseday.com or use any of the Releaseday Services to ensure you are familiar with the most updated policies and practices

**How does Releaseday work with social networks such as Facebook?**

  * Releaseday and Social Networking.

If you choose to link your Releaseday account with a social networking service, Releaseday and that service may share certain information about you and your activities. With your consent, we also may share information about your activities, including what you watch on Releaseday, with that social network’s users.

  * Connecting with Facebook While Using the Releaseday Services.

Facebook and Releaseday have developed a process that allows you to connect your Releaseday account with your Facebook account. When you connect your accounts, you authorize Releaseday and Facebook to share certain information about you with each other..

When you choose to share information about your activities on Releaseday with Facebook, Facebook may make that information visible to Facebook users in accordance with applicable law, the [Facebook Data Use Policy](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy), and your Facebook privacy settings. You can always stop or start sharing your activities on Releaseday with Facebook at any time using the [Account > Privacy and Settings](https://www.releaseday.com/user-account/privacyPolicy) controls on Releaseday.

  * Sharing on Releaseday

When you connect your Releaseday and Facebook accounts, Releaseday will access the list of all your Facebook friends and import them to Releaseday. All of your Facebook friends who have also connected their Releaseday and Facebook accounts will be connected to you on Releaseday. Any Facebook friend who connects his or her Releaseday and Facebook accounts at a later date will also automatically be connected to you on Releaseday. This means that, if you choose to share your activities on Releaseday, all of your Facebook friends who have connected their Facebook and Releaseday accounts will be able to see what you watch when they use Releaseday. You can always stop or start sharing your activities on the Releaseday Service at any time using the [Account > Privacy and Settings](https://www.releaseday.com/user-account/privacyPolicy) controls on Releaseday.

  * Separate Lists of Friends

Although Releaseday imports all of your friends from Facebook, the Releaseday and Facebook privacy settings are separate. This means that your Facebook privacy controls do not control who can see your activity on Releaseday. As a result, if you choose to connect your Facebook and Releaseday accounts and enable sharing, then all of your Facebook friends will be able to see your Releaseday activity when they use Releaseday.

  * In addition, if you visit Releaseday while logged into Facebook, then Facebook may be able to identify you and to associate the technical information provided by your web browser with other information that Facebook already has about you.
